blinky.co.nz 2010-11-23

# Free Samples, competitions and vouchers |

* **

## Privacy policy

**  
As a condition to using the Service, you agree to the terms of the Blinky.co.nz privacy policy as it may be updated from time to time. Blinky.co.nz understands that privacy is important to you. You do, however, agree that Blinky.co.nz may monitor, edit or disclose your personal information, including the content of your emails, if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order), or as otherwise provided in these Terms of Use and the Blinky.co.nz Privacy Policy. Personal information collected by Blinky.co.nz may be stored and processed in the New Zealand. Blinky.co.nz will not sell or rent your email address or details. 

## **Google and the[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the [NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.
